Date and Attendees: 9/20; David, Aishwarya, Aashish, Eva, Jen


Methods of Communication:
Weekly meeting time (changed): Saturday ~1PM on TEAMS
Phone group chat for quick updates



Agenda:

Discussing data/base options

David: we can use dummy database instead to build functionality before real data

Aashish: can generate dummy data from chatgpt
	potential webapp alternatives to flask: vercel, railway (javascript). Could be easier than apache.

Ash: has found GIS data, can be loaded into a database
	Can enter a flat file (.csv) into database
	Can make an excel sheet categorizing health services
	Example health directory dashboard from geobluedirectory
		Lifted html from page

Selenium webscraping demo from David, recording available on teams. Documentation here; https://selenium-python.readthedocs.io/
	
GUI examples:
	https://www.medicare.gov/care-compare/?providerType=Hospital
	health directory dashboard from geobluedirectory



What is considered "done" (this week):
	Database schema design (5 columns)
	GUI for search by location, search by service pages

Looking ahead (next week): webapp development



TO DO:

GUI/UI/UX: Eva, Jen
	figma invite: https://www.figma.com/team_invite/redeem/kBAVO5LltP1kvs8o3Ltbvj
Sample data excel sheet or .csv file: Ash
Webapp platform setup: David, Aashish


Misc: Ash would like to listen in/observe on people's work for learning purposes
	Also opens opportunity for critique (ie. UI feasibility)