Date and Attendees: 9/27; David, Aishwarya, Aashish, Eva, Jen


Ash and Eva: new .csv's in drive and github
David: filtered new data in Jupyter pandas

Ash: facility name is available, but not list of physicians
	Public Medi-Cal list is available, private networks are not available
Eva: What's the difference between provider and facility?
	Provider = Physician, Facility = Hospital


AGENDA: PART B due OCT 2

1. [done]Decompose your user stories into tasks. 
2. [done]Outline what features will be in Milestone 1.0 of your project.
	MVP 1. Search by Category
	   Search by Provider

	Eva and Ash: CHANGE "Update Provider Offerings" to "Update Facility Offerings"
	Eva: (for future consideration) "Update Facility Offerings" needs login/account system. Move login feature up to priority 1.
	(Looking ahead, not due)
	MVP 1. Create account
	     Update Provider/Facility Offerings
	
3. Build the iterations (at most 2) that will compose your Milestone 1.0. Record the total days of work and the time it will take for your team to complete that work. Be sure to account for velocity before breaking into iterations.

4. [done]Allocate tasks to each team member and record the allocation.

	Task(days)
	(0.5) Define scope and objectives
	(0.5) Identify stakeholders (patients, providers, administrators, IT teams, executives)
	(0.5) Assign team roles and responsibilities
	(0.5) Create initial timeline and milestones
	(7)   Design core service database schema
		Browse Services by Category
		Search for Services by Location
		Filter services by provider/facility
		View Detailed Provider Information
	(3) Search Data

	--- vv IN PROGRESS vv ---
	1(3) Create Data
		Can start with "HospitalGenInfo" on github
		Needed fields: 0-13 columns
		Things for consideration: How to merge dataset if Facility ID is different?
	2(7) Develop backend query processing & filtering {SQL query or Pandas}
		When querying, return listings within the same zipcode
	3(14) User Management: create Account (Patients, Providers, Admins), enable role-based access
	4(14) Provider Management: display and update provider offerings
	5(?) Admin Tools
	6(3) Design UI
	7(1) Design Review
	8(7) Build UI components
	9(7) Testing
	10(1) Documentation
	11(7) Presentation Prep

5. [Eva, David?]Create a burn down chart for monitoring your team’s progress.
	Scrum: Check in on Saturday during meeting, Tues by 9pm
	Report 3 things on TEAMS SCRUM CHANNEL: what I completed, what I am doing/will do next, what impedes me

6. [done]Provide evidence in your github repository that you are meeting for periodic stand up meetings - your team should ideally meet at least twice a week (meeting agenda, log, etc.)

7. Ensure that your development and testing environment is set up. Be sure to have some working functional (however rudimentary) and test code in your repository.

