Date and Attendees: 11/1; David, Eva, Aashish, Aishwarya, Jen



Finishing up Milestone 1:

What's left to be done; implement patient reviews and admin panel

Make sure the codebase runs in other environment; David, Aashish, and Jen provide instructions on how to run the app/tests




Discussing  Milestone 2:

Ash: Need to change Maternity Care to Women's Health because Medi-care population is elderly

(User story 4, HIGH prio) Admin panel requirements:
	- User management page that displays a list of users/info
	- info includes: name, email, username, status, role, join date, etc
	- need to tweak database for users
	- David: database doesn't persist between machines, maybe bcrypt is not working as intended? (stopgap, make a dummy list of users to insert into the database)

(User story 5) No longer makes sense because we don't have names of individual physicians

(User story 6, LOW prio) Provider update options
	

(User story 7, MED prio)


Eva: will take 1 week to research and try to get geocoding/proximity search working



TODO: David, Aashish: finish up milestone 1
		      User story 4 and 7
      Eva: Investigate proximity search
      Jen, Aishwarya: UI/UX for user story 4/7
      Jen: testing