Date and Attendees: 11/19; David, Aishwarya, Jen, Aashish, Eva


DEMOING THE CURRENT APP

Permissions are working
Features are exclusive to their role (reviews for user, not for provider)
Admin panel functions incomplete
	-Admin CAN swap roles
	-Cannot update provider

Aashish: demoing another branch with provider and admin functions
	- Manage hospital services function working for admins
		- Ash: let provider and admins both access this

David and Ash: want to add another button to search page to go directly to reviews


UPDATING THE README

TODO: 

Jen update test instr
Jen and Ash fill out test strategies summary section
David fill out GitHub Actions section



USER STORY STATUS

User Story 4: Create New Accounts
	UPDATE USER STORY TO: Manage Accounts
		Account management is complete

User Story 5: Update Provider Offerings
	Mostly done

User Story 6: Ratings and Reviews
	done for the purpose of the presentation
	- David: backend database functionality challenges can be talked about in presentation


Eva: @David, any missing functionalities or bugs can be added to GitHub issues page
	- eg. "Ratings Need to Show Average User Ratings"



DISCUSSING PRESENTATION SLIDES

TODO: everyone fill out something on Success and Failures, slide ~33

David: everyone can talk about the lessons learned as it applied to them

 - Software Development Slide
	Requirement & Plans Evolve: open w/ Ash
 	Break Down Big Tasks: open w/ David
	Collaborate Consistently: open w/ Eva
	
Plan to come in early before class if possible