Date: 9/13/2025 

Attendees: David, Aashish, Eva, Jen

Methods of communication hereon:
	Weekly meeting time (generally): Saturday ~2PM on Zoom through CGU email
	Phone group chat for quick updates




AGENDA: 

Discuss and define the tasks and estimate time according to "effort points".

Define what is "Done"
	Eva: Coding segments need to be demonstratable, test code needs to be testable, design needs 	to fit the brief
		



LOOKING AHEAD to week 6's assignment: Pick two most important tasks (merge some)
	
User Stories (MVP): 	Browse Services by Category
			Search for Services by Location
			View Detailed Provider Information
			Provider Offerings
			Update Provider Offerings
			
User notes: 	Need to allow patients to search by name of facility, type of service needed
		Allow providers to login and add new services to their facility
		Allow administrators to add, edit , or remove items in catalogue




TASKS: 	- find data of medical facilities and offered services (needs to have category)
	- data cleaning (category cleanup)
	- set up database (where to host?)
		David: Not ideal, but Prof said we can use a dummy database if needed
	- load data into database
	- design API to access the database
	- set up web server to host flask app (apache or tomcat, local machine server?)
		Aashish: nginx as alternative?
		Flask tutorials: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL-osiE80TeTs4UjLw5MM6OjgkjFeUxCYH
	- design web application workflow (see user notes above)
	- design app UI/UX
	- web development
	- QA, create test cases and report results

TO DO by WEEK 6 (effort points):
	- download data: Ash, Eva, Jen (1)
		Resource? https://business.yelp.com/data/resources/open-dataset/
	- data clean up: Eva, David (?)
	- UI/UX design: Jen (3)
	- Design review: together (1, next meeting)
	- Flask/ web app development: David, Aashish (tbd)
	- data setup and hosting: Eva (2)
	- database loading: Eva (?)
	- setup application server: Aashish (3)
	- QA: TBD

Misc: Pull request for QA work?