Date and Attendees: 11/17; David, Jen, Eva, Aashish



David: was having trouble with implementing roles for the admin panel and password handling, but should be fixed now

Aashish: made a new fork with review system. Button is on the homepage.
	- Should move this functionality to the hospital details page


TODO:

Eva: update the readme, work on the slide deck that will serve as an outline for our presentation

David: refine role access for admin panel

Aashish: add review functionality to other pages

Jen: implement pytest coverage and tests for review syste,