Date and Attendees: 10/4; Eva, Aashish, Aishwarya, Jen, David



AGENDA: Scrum check-ins

Aashish: working on frontend
	What's next: creating UI buttons
David: working on setting up SQL database
	Impediment: finding resources to understand database integration
	What's next: create separate table for login credentials
Jen: working on UI, finished views from patient/user side
	What's next: finish views for admin and provider side
Aish: N/A
	What's next: N/A
Eva: updated README and burndown chart
	What's next: break down task list into dashboard with iteration and milestones



TO DO FOR EVERYONE: do some research on how to link front end to backend via Flask
	how to get frontend to talk to the database

NEXT WEEK'S AGENDA: review UI, then coding interface can begin