Date and Attendees: 10/19; David, Aishwarya, Jen, Aashish, Eva

Agenda:

CONFIRM WHICH USER STORIES STATUS/COMPLETION: First 3 should be done

Ash: 	-combine a couple of user stories; search by hospital, name, city, zip
	-services is not functional; make up fake columns in database to create a 		dropdown filter
David:	Or filtering through checkbox
Ash:	-what to do about HIPPA with login credentials?
	-add external links to expanded detail page
Eva:	-change services to TYPE of hospital
Ash:	-skip emergency category, make acute(urgent) care

Current hospital type columns: 
	Acute Care Hospitals                    71
	Psychiatric                             12
	Acute Care - Veterans Administration     2
	Childrens                                2
	Critical Access Hospitals 		 1

David: filtering with dropdown options? should we separate SEARCH and BROWSE pages?




Confirming Features on Figma

Eva: Search by City; potential for user spelling error
Aashish: Can leave fuzzy search for the next milestone

David: we can streamline user experience by combining hospital name and type
	Under Search by Type: need to consider geo-spatial search for next milestone
		e.g. If someone's searching for Urgent Care, probably want the closest one

Confirming Frontend with Aashish
	Login works! 	Username: admin
			Password: admin123

	David: Administrator needs to have power to change normal user to provider and a screen for that (for milestone 2)




DISCUSS PRESENTATION DETAILS

	Everyone in-person!
	
1. Eva: 	introduce the app
2. Ash: 	user stories from your perspective
3. Eva: 	project itself and burndown/meetings
4. David, Aashish: demo the app
	David talk about search hospital by name, type, zip, etc
	Aashish talk about browse by hospital type
	don't show everything that is good, show errors
		David; if someone types something bad, show 'no results found'
5. Ash: acceptance criteria
6. Jen: present tests
7. Eva: conclusion
