Date and Attendees: 10/11; David, Aishwarya, Jen, Eva, Aashish



AGENDA:

->Missing pieces: acceptance criteria

TODO: 
Acceptance criteria - Ash (collab w/ Jen)
Write test cases (conceptual skeleton) - Jen (collab w/ Ash)
	i.e. test return of information for [criteria] filtering



->Discuss flask + database connection
	
Stick to the functionalities similar to what's already in the recent flask blog homework, no JSON or other bells and whistles
Think small for now, as long as it runs

TODO:
Flask collaboration - David, Aashish


->Discuss project C presentation


"	1. Present to your class Milestone 1.0 of your project. Each team member must present 	a portion of the team presentation.
	2. You must present working code. In addition, your presentation must include:
		What the code does
		How it fulfills the user stories
		Documentation of the use of agile methods
		explanation of how the code was tested
	3. Explain what remains to be done to accomplish Milestone 2.0.
"	4. Upload any presentation materials in your repository in a folder named "Part C".


TENTATIVE PRESENTATION OUTLINE
1. Eva intro project and functionality
2. David and Aashish talk about code and how to fulfill user story + demo
3. Ash talk about acceptance criteria as project owner
4. Jen talk about test code based on acceptance criteria
5. Eva talks about group agile methods and burndown chart
6. ??? talk about Milestone 2.0
7. Eva outro


->Discuss UI/UX
	Move Urgent Care to home landing screen possibly(?)
	Administrator panel: view to add/remove new hospitals, services
		screen to input listings' address, name, zip, etc fields

TODO: 
Finish admin panel, fix backward navigation - Jen
